displaymarketplace.com 2008-09-15

# Emediate Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy for Emediate advertising service**

Users may use Emediate ad serving technology when they visit websites or advertisers using Emediates ad serving technology (EAS). Emediate asks all clients using our ad serving technology to disclose their relationship with us by providing notice to consumers about the Emediate technologies. Emediate also asks clients that use our ad serving technology to link from their privacy policy to ours to allow consumers to opt-out of the Emediate ad-serving cookie. 

Emediate believes that Internet consumers should be able to control the use of their information. We provide Internet users the choice not to have online information collected about them from their browsers during ad serving by providing an anonymous cookie. 

Emediate has implemented generally accepted standards of technology security in order to protect information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Only authorized Emediate personnel and agents are provided access to personal information and databases containing non-personal information. 

As Emediate introduces new products and services changes are made to existing products, Emediate reserves the right to amend this policy at any time. All privacy policies are dated with the effective date. Information collected about you by us under a particular policy is used in the manner disclosed to you at the time it was collected, unless Emediate obtains your agreement to use your information in a different way. 

Emediate may transfer information to a company that provides services that assist Emediate in its business. Those companies act as our agents and are bound to use the information only for the purposes for which Emediate has shared the information. If Emediate transfers information to third parties for other purposes, those parties are required to apply the same notice and choice principles to which Emediate uses. 

The client website who use Emediates ad serving technology have complete ownership of all the data associated with the campaigns they serve, including the user data. 

On occasion, advertisers or websites may provide Emediate with non-personally-identifiable demographic information so that you may receive ads that more closely match the users interests. This information is handled with the same privacy protections as the Emediate-collected non-personally-identifiable information. 

**Emediates use of cookies:**  
In order to create and deliver functionality Emediate uses cookies to: 

* Report to Emediates advertiser and Web site clients the estimated total reach of an ad campaign 
* Report the frequency with which an ad was shown to a user 
* Ensure that an advertisement displayed to a user corresponds to the correct click-through destination 
* Deliver a series of advertisements in the proper sequence 
* Limit the number of times a browser is delivered the same advertisement. 

**Emediate uses the following types of non-personally-identifiable information about users who are served ads via Emediate technology:**  

* IP address (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet). Information which Emediate can use from the IP address is the user's geographic location and company name. 
* Users domain type (, .com, .net). 
* Standard information included with every communication sent on the Internet such as browser version and type (i.e., Netscape or Internet Explorer), operating system (i.e., windows or DOS), browser language (i.e., Java or Unix), service provider, users local time, etc. 
* The ads delivered to the users browser and the pages the user visit on a website using Emediate technology.
